<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeeZone</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="app_home_heading">About the App</string>
    <string name="app_home_content">This App provides a variety of tools to enable you to take a break from a racing, stressful mind and come back to calmness and focus.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_the_app">About the App</string>
    <string name="med">Meditation</string>
    <string name="meditation_introduction">The process of meditation teaches us the art of connecting with our consciousness and changing it from one based on a physical reality to one that is non-physical – a spiritual reality.
As you make your way through this process you will naturally go through a number of steps to reach a state of meditation. Your experience at each step will be beautiful, enriching and empowering, but it is only the final step that is referred to as actual ‘meditation’.
</string>
    <string name="steps_of_meditation">5 Steps of Meditation</string>
    <string name="relaxation">Relaxation</string>
    <string name="relaxation_description">Relaxation is about letting go of tension and stress and bringing the mind and body into a state of calm and peace …</string>
    <string name="concentration">Concentration</string>
    <string name="concentration_description">Concentration allows me to use my time productively, once I have relaxed: I can focus on the thoughts I choose to have …</string>
    <string name="contemplation">Contemplation</string>
    <string name="contemplation_description">Contemplation is reflecting deeply on myself, my inner world and my values…</string>
    <string name="realisation">Realisation</string>
    <string name="realisation_description">Realisation is when my understanding and feelings combine and I experience a more profound, more meaningful reality…</string>
    <string name="meditation_description">Meditation is focusing on a thought and remembering my eternal identity, and re-awakening a wonderful state of well-being …</string>
    <string name="approach">Our Approach</string>
    <string name="approach_para1">Raja Yoga Meditation is based on a body of knowledge. Through understanding one is able to create a state of spiritual awareness.
    </string>
    <string name="approach_para2">This art of self-awareness, by learning to use our mind in the right way, enables one to become a master over our own life, and the experiences we have in life.
    </string>
    <string name="approach_para3">We gently guide and direct our mind in a chosen direction, thinking only peaceful, positive and empowering thoughts, and then go into the experience of them.
    </string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="bkwsu">Brahma Kumaris World Spiritual University</string>
    <string name="bkwsu_description">Brahma Kumaris is a worldwide spiritual movement dedicated to personal transformation and world renewal. Founded in India in 1937, Brahma Kumaris has spread to over 110 countries on all continents and has had an extensive impact in many sectors as an international NGO. However, their real commitment is to helping individuals transform their perspective of the world from material to spiritual. It supports the cultivation of a deep collective consciousness of peace and of the individual dignity of each soul. The University offers all its activities free of charge, being funded by voluntary contributions.</string>
    <string name="app_desc2">It can be used by anyone at anytime to Stop – Relax – Experience – Re-Empower.</string>
    <string name="daily_challenge">Daily Challenge</string>
    <string name="Virtuescope">Virtuescope</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic">Mood Clinic</string>
    <string name="mind_gym">Mind Gym</string>
    <string name="mind_lab">Mind Lab</string>
    <string name="mind_spa">Mind Spa</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="daily_about">A fresh challenge each day to inculcate a virtue into your daily life.</string>
    <string name="mind_gym_heading">Mind Gym has some focusing or relaxation exercises to keep the mind fit and healthy</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_heading">Mind Spa is a collection of meditation audios to relax and unwind. Please select the ones you like from the list and relax…</string>
    <string name="virtue_about">Spin the Virtue Wheel and Meditate on your personal virtue of the day</string>
    <string name="mc_about">Select your mood and allow our guided mediations to help shift that mood.</string>
    <string name="mg_about">Here we have some focusing or relaxation exercises to keep the mind fit and healthy.</string>
    <string name="ml_about">Try one of our meditation techniques to help you relax and refocus.</string>
    <string name="ms_about">A variety of meditation audios to relax and unwind.</string>
    <string name="focus_ex">Focus Exercise</string>
    <string name="breathing_ex">De-Stress Exercise</string>
    <string name="meditate_button">Meditate Now</string>
    <string name="experiment_button">Experiment Now</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_home_content">Try one of our meditation techniques to help you relax and refocus</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_content_breathing">Using breath as a means to focus</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_desc_om_chant">Expand your consciousness with the eternal sound of the Universe....</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_desc_relaxation">Relax the body and mind with this step-by-step commentary</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_desc_the_conch">Journey to the depths of your unlimited self</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_desc_5_steps_to_meditate">5 Steps to Meditation</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_music_desc_tibetan_singing">Healing vibrations to releases emotional blockages</string>
    <string name="tc_hourly">Hourly</string>
    <string name="tc_hourly_2_hours">Every 2 hours</string>
    <string name="tc_no_entries">BeeZone Traffic Control is empty and cannot be started</string>
    <string name="title_activity_traffic_control">TrafficControlActivity</string>
    <string name="button_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="bigger_than">></string>
    <string name="week_day_sunday">Every Sunday</string>
    <string name="week_day_monday">Every Monday</string>
    <string name="week_day_tuesday">Every Tuesday</string>
    <string name="week_day_wednesday">Every Wednesday</string>
    <string name="week_day_thursday">Every Thursday</string>
    <string name="week_day_friday">Every Friday</string>
    <string name="week_day_saturday">Every Saturday</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_breathing_technique">Breathing Technique</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_tibetan_singing_bowls">Tibetan Singing Bowls</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_om_chant">Om Chant</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_relaxation">Relaxation</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_the_conch_shell">The Conch Shell</string>
    <string name="mind_lab_5_steps_to_meditate">5 Steps to Meditation</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_upset">Upset</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_angry">Angry</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_anxious">Anxious</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_confused">Confused</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_feeling_down">Feeling Down</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_jealous">Jealous</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_lonely">Lonely</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_negative">Negative</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_sad">Sad</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_scared">Scared</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_sensitive">Sensitive</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_stressed">Stressed</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_upset_transform">Transform Upset</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_angry_transform">Transform Anger</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_anxious_transform">Transform Anxiety</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_confused_transform">Transform Confusion</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_feeling_down_transform">Uplift Spirit</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_jealous_transform">Transform Jealousy</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_lonely_transform">Transform Loneliness</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_negative_transform">Transform Negativity</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_sad_transform">Transform Sadness</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_scared_transform">Transform Fear</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_sensitive_transform">Transform Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="mood_clinic_stressed_transform">Transform Stress</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_a_quiet_place">A Quiet Place to be</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_amber_evening">Amber Evening</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_ancient_lores">Ancient Lores</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_aura_light">Aura of Light</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_cosmos">Cosmos</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_golden_chains">Golden Chains</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_hide_seek">Hide and Seek</string>
    <string name="mind_spa_indian_summer">Indian Summer</string>
    <string name="favourites_no_favourite_yet">No Favourite yet. Click on the hearts to create one …</string>
    <string name="daily_dismiss_instructions">Hide Instructions</string>
    <string name="daily_explanation">A daily Food for Thought, for a healthy and happy mind. Your Challenge: Contemplate and Apply the days\' virtue into your daily schedule.</string>
    <string name="general_do_not_display_again">Do not display this message again</string>
    <string name="traffic_control">Traffic Control</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_about_description">Create moments throughout the day to pause the traffic of your thoughts and refocus the mind.</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_notification">Traffic control coming up next at %1$d %2$s</string>
    <string name="notification_beezone">BeeZone notifications</string>
    <string name="contact_us_title">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="web_character">🌏</string>
    <string name="http_bee_zone">http://bee.zone</string>
    <string name="contact_us_target_email">beezone@bkconnect.net</string>
    <string name="contact_us_subject">✍ Subject</string>
    <string name="contact_us_subject_edit">Beezone feedback …</string>
    <string name="contact_us_body">✍ Your message</string>
    <string name="contact_us_body_edit">More feedback …</string>
    <string name="contact_us_send_feedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_text">Beezone app for Android: </string>
    <string name="select_time">Select notification time</string>
    <string name="notification_on">Notification on</string>
    <string name="notification_off">Notification off</string>
    <string name="songadapter_cannot_reschedule_songs">Could not reschedule songs: %s</string>
    <string name="songadapter_cannot_reschedule">Could not reschedule songs: %s</string>
    <string name="songadapter_select_one">At least one song needs to be selected</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_boot_receiver_schedule_started">Beezone %s schedule started</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_boot_receiver_schedule_failed">Beezone schedule could not start</string>
    <string name="about_dialogue_current_version">Current version: %s - %d</string>
    <string name="daily_fragment_daily_challenge">Daily Challenge</string>
    <string name="favourites_fragment_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="favourite_song_adapter_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_getting_started">Getting Started with the app</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_app_features">What are the app features?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_length_meditation_sessions">How long are the meditation sessions?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_who_app_for">Who is this app for?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_ry_med">Raja Yoga Meditation</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_what_is_med">What is meditation?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_why_med">Why meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_kind_of_med">What kind of meditation is Raja Yoga?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditation_help">How does meditation help?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_anyone">Can anyone learn to meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_ry_med_benefits">What are the benefits of Raja Yoga meditation?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_learn_how_long">How long will it take to learn?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_why_no_charges">Why don\'t you charge for your product?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_why_free">How to learn deep meditation?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_tips">Tips for Meditation</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_when_med">When should I meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_time_for_med">How do I find time to meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_where_med">Where should I meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_clothes">What should I wear to meditate?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_sit">How do I sit during meditation?</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_daily_challenge">Daily Challenge: A fresh challenge each day to inculcate a virtue into daily life.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_virtuescope">Virtuescope: Spin the Virtue Wheel and Meditate on your personal virtue of the day.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_mood_clinic">Mood Clinic: Select your mood and allow our guided meditations to help shift that mood.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_mind_gym">Mind Gym: Here we have some focusing or relaxation exercises to keep the mind fit and healthy.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_mind_lab">Mind Lab: Try one of our mediation techniques to help you relax and refocus.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_mind_spa">Mind Spa: A variety of meditation audios to relax and unwind.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditation_length_explanation">We have aimed to make each session of meditation on this about 5 minutes long so that it is more practical to incorporate into a busy schedule. If you wish to experiment with longer meditation sessions can be found on http://www.brahmakumaris.org/meditation/experience-meditation .</string>
    <string name="hemp_fragment_target_audience">The app is aimed at people with a busy life who wish to start introducing meditation practices into their routine. It provides some simple tools to allow one to stop, re-empower internally, and then continue with activity having shifted their state of mind.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditation_journey_inwards">Meditation is the journey inwards, a journey of self-discovery or, in fact, re-discovery. Meditation is time taken for quiet reflection and silence, away from the hustle and bustle of daily living. Taking time out enables us to come back to a centred place of being.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditation_state_of_being">Meditation is a state of being in that place just beyond every day consciousness, which is where spiritual empowerment begins. Spiritual awareness gives us the power to choose good and positive thoughts over those which are negative and wasteful. We start to respond to situations, rather than just reacting to them. We begin to live with harmony, we create better and happier, healthier relationships and change our lives in a most positive way. Raja Yoga teaches us to step back and observe life, take a calm breath, cool our reactions, and step forward in the way we choose - independent of others urging us to think or act as they wish.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_ry_meditation_explanation">Raja Yoga meditation is a form of meditation that is accessible to people of all backgrounds. It is a meditation without rituals or mantras and can be practised anywhere at any time. Raja Yoga meditation is practised with ‘open eyes\', which makes this method of meditation versatile, simple and easy to practice.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_ancient_meditation">This ancient meditation practice harnesses your natural powers and trains your mind to be your friend.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditation_spiritual_empowerment">Meditation is a state of being in that place just beyond every day consciousness, which is where spiritual empowerment begins. Spiritual awareness gives us the power to choose good and positive thoughts over those which are negative and wasteful. We start to respond to situations, rather than just reacting to them. We begin to live with harmony, we create better and happier, healthier relationships and change our lives in a most positive way.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_ry_step_back">Raja Yoga teaches us to step back and observe life, take a calm breath, cool our reactions, and step forward in the way we choose - independent of others urging us to think or act as they wish.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_anyone_can_benefit">Anyone and everyone who wants to can use, and benefit from, Raja Yoga meditation. Some choose to connect with a centre of meditation, like the Brahma Kumaris, others incorporate meditation into their daily lives and work with it themselves. It all works and it all enriches the lives of those who choose it.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_as_empowerment">Meditation is a state of being in that place just beyond every day consciousness, which is where spiritual empowerment begins. Spiritual awareness gives us the power to choose good and positive thoughts over those which are negative and wasteful. We start to respond to situations, rather than just reacting to them. We begin to live with harmony, we create better and happier, healthier relationships and change our lives in a most positive way.</string>
    <string name="hemp_fragment_ry_observing_life">Raja Yoga teaches us to step back and observe life, take a calm breath, cool our reactions, and step forward in the way we choose - independent of others urging us to think or act as they wish.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_med_as_discipline">Like any discipline or form of art, it required one to invest time and energy to learn. It all depends on the individual and their commitment to practice.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_prod_development">This product has been developed by people who actively practice meditation in their lives and have taken a lot benefit from it. It has been distributed free of charge so that it is accessible to anyone who wish to explore meditation without a need to be able to afford it.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_connect_to_centre">It is suggested that if you would like to explore Raja Yoga Meditation further then you connect with a Brahma Kumaris centre in your locality. The list of locations can be found on their website at http://www.brahmakumaris.org/centre-locator</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditate_at_any_time">You can meditate any time of the day but creating a habit of early morning meditation, before starting the day, is very beneficial as there are fewer distractions at that time and it allows you to ‘set yourself up’ for the day in a positive and empowering way.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_make_time">Like anything, you need to make time. It is so easy to convince the self that you have no time and so during the early stages of practice it is necessary to be disciplined. Once you start seeing the benefit you will naturally make time for it.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_meditate_anywhere">You can actually meditate anywhere but it is good to try and make a space in your home where you meditate each day. This will help create an energy and vibration which will, over time, naturally attract you into meditation.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_no_specific_rules">There are no specific rules on what to wear as this meditation works with the mind and not the body. However wearing something light and comfortable is good.</string>
    <string name="help_fragment_no_specific_rules_long">Sit comfortably, but in an upright position. It can be on the floor or a chair. What is important is that the body is comfortable. Once you start meditating you don’t want to be distracted by for sitting position.</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_fragment_tc_off">Traffic Control turned off</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_fragment_tc_on_next_alarm">Traffic Control turned on. Next alarm at: %02d:%02d</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_reschedule_failed">Could not re-schedule traffic control: %s</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_fragment_chosen_period_invalid">The chosen period is not valid. Please make sure that the start time is before the end time</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_segment_rescheduled">Traffic control re-scheduled and coming up next at %02d:%02d</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_repeat_fragment_schedule_activated">%s schedule activated</string>
    <string name="traffic_control_repeat_fragment_schedule_active_fail">%s schedule could not be activated</string>
</resources>